What are you doing, huh?
And what are you doing there
in the secret door of agents? Huh?
How did you know that?
I'm the one who told him about it.
But, Mikoy, what are you doing here?
Come here.
I just miss you.
Do you feel the same thing about me?
I'm just joking!
Come on! You look so tense.
I'm here because I got fresh information.
This one! Do you all see that?
This is where all the files
of Vertex's drivers came from.
I cracked down on all
the local operations of the Moraviano.
And I know how to bring them down.
Are you there?
What the heck!
You're the one acting crazy.
You look like you've seen a ghost.
It's just that…
I got traumatized by what I watched.
What was it?
That ‘Taiwan Killer Hospital' thing.
It really traumatized me.
- Why?
- Well, that's what you get
for watching stuff like that without me.
Sorry, sweetheart. I just got excited.
But I'm free now.
Come on, do you want to binge-watch
horror movies together?
Not anymore, sweetheart.
Actually, I wanted to ask
for your permission.
You don't love me anymore?
You're being so dramatic!
No, it's not that.
My dad needs me to fix some things.
So, like what?
He doesn't want it neglected.
I thought it was something else.
So, when are you coming back?
I'm not sure.
But one thing I'm sure of…
Is that when I come back,
we're gonna have the best time ever.
Do you want to finally go through
with our travel plans?
Really?
Yes!
Yes, of course!
Okay, promise me?
Viktor is probably already wondering
why you've been gone for hours.
And if he discovers that
you failed to kill me,
what do you think he'll think of you?
She's right.
So now, I'll show you our target.
I just wanted to try.
And it has a delivery scheduled
this Friday at Ignacio Port.
Here.
I also made my own storyboard
so we'll know and visualize
what could happen.
And based on the information
given by Mikoy,
shipments at Ignacio Port
are consistently delayed by 1-2 hours.
Given the loading time,
it shouldn't be far from
the port's 5-10 km radius.
I'll handle the traffic control.
I will coordinate with
the local police units
and make sure no one interferes
with our operation.
And all we need to do is
seize one cargo container
and that should be enough
for us to get a court order
to investigate Vertex.
- Sianong.
- Yes?
I can't find him in his office.
Where is he?
At home.
Where else would I go?
Dear…
Stress doesn't make you beautiful.
Do you want to get wrinkles?
Yes, I know you.
How can I not worry?
After everything I found out from Sianong.
Damn that Sianong.
What did he tell you?
How can I protect you
if you're keeping me in the dark?
From the moment I wake up,
every move I make,
my feet are already in the grave.
For your future, for all your futures.
Sofie.
You have to be strong, dear.
If anything happens to me,
You go to your sister Alex.
And those VHZ tapes under my bed,
dispose of them, okay?
I don't care!
Don't worry, my dear.
We've been through this a lot of times.
And I'm still here, standing, fighting.
We can't stop our lives from running,
just because my life is under threat.
And Sofie, what did I tell you?
That you're more likely
to die in a car accident,
than for enemies to kill you.
Because you are still the legendary
‘Sharpshooting Executioner of Mindoro'.
That's right. And remember that.
See you later, dear.
Hold on.
Have a seat first.
I'm getting tired of looking up at you.
What exactly are you worried about?
That Norberto guy is an easy target.
They're no match for our daughter.
Is this my last hour?
Dad?!
Dad…
what are you doing here?
And what's this?
Why did you point your gun at me?
It's a test.
A test?! Dad, I'm not in school anymore.
Not that kind of test.
And why do you even have a gun?
I'm testing you to see if you can handle
what you got yourself into.
Mikoy, I know everything.
I also know about
your double life as an asset.
And I also know the true
identity of Viktor Valtrovi.
How?
You look like you're searching
for something.
Thanks, but…
my wife's frying pan hits
way harder than that.
And that's not what I'm buying.
So what are you buying?
Just liquor?
Actually, he's looking for me, Rosa.
You have a request in the VIP room.
Go dance there first.
Fine, Mama.
So that's your type.
The infamous Catacutan.
Oh, my gosh!
You go to girly bars?
For me to get an information.
Information? Stop lying!
I'm telling Mom about this.
What?
You're telling your mom? Try it.
Your eyes will be the only thing
without bruises.
Whoa, I was just joking, Dad.
You're so harsh.
Mikoy, enough joking around.
Tell me everything now,
and this time
only the truth.
Mikoy, do you even understand
what you've gotten yourself into?
Raise your hands.
So my agents were right…
you really are left-handed.
Face me.
Turn around.
You thought I would be easy to kill?
Because of your mistake,
you're caught now.
Looks like you can feel it,
that my men have surrounded this place.
This is just bait
to make you think I was alone
and you took the bait.
Bok, relax.
Don't worry, as I said earlier,
the tac teams and Agent Kian
are already there, okay?
They're nearby, and if ever
something bad happens
they are always ready to move in
in seconds.
Be ready.
Now, you have nowhere left to run.
You seem taller than in the report
or maybe I'm mistaken.
Maybe it's better not to.
Because once you see my face,
you're as good as dead.
You're not in position to make threats.
You're surrounded.
You have nowhere left to go.
You should know that.
That sharp-shooting butcher
is such a stupid bastard.
He told me you weren't involved.
Huh?!
Who's a butcher, Dad?
It's Sianong, right?
Mikoy.
There's nothing you can do now,
you're already too deep in.
You have no choice.
You have to finish this.
Mikoy, out of everything,
why did you choose this?
Why did you agree to it?
I didn't want this, Dad.
I was just blackmailed.
Those idiots really used you.
Yes Dad, from the start.
But after I found out
what was really happening,
of course it reached a point where
I made my own choice.
I decided to become a part of this.
Why?
This whole mess is dangerous.
What were you thinking? And for what?
For Chiara.
Dad, I want to protect her.
From her family's world.
Protect her?
Protect her?!
You really think she knows nothing?
You think Chiara doesn't know
the kind of world her parents live in?
- She got out!
- Medic!
- She escaped!
You!
Looks like she got
shot her clothes have blood.
We might know her.
This is not Henry.
What's that look on your face?
Why did you tell him?
Are you sure?
Because we found out that you're injured.
It rains, it pours.
It's been one setback after another.
Do I need to know something?
I don't believe it, Dad.
You're wrong about Chiara.
Those kind of syndicates, they're family.
That's why I believe Chiara
knows about it.
And I wouldn't be surprise if one day,
she will inherit the syndicate
her family's running.